In this very short video, I'm going to say a few words about a technique called
在这段很短的视频中，我将简单介绍一种名为
Conservative Garbage Collection that can be used for languages like C and C++. To
保守垃圾回收，可用于C和C++等语言。至
review, Automatic Memory Management relies on being able to find all the reachable
回顾一下，自动内存管理依赖于能够找到所有可访问的
objects. And it also needs to be able to find all the pointers in an object. Now,
对象。它还需要能够找到对象中的所有指针。现在,
the difficultly with doing garbage collection for a language like C or C++ is
对C或C++这样的语言执行垃圾回收的困难在于
that it's very difficult or even impossible to identify the contents of
很难甚至不可能辨认出
objects in memory with 100 percent reliability. So if we see, two words in
对象以100%的可靠性存储在内存中。所以如果我们看到，有两个词
memory, you know, it might be a list cell that has, a data and next field. So we see
内存，你知道，它可能是一个列表单元格，它有一个数据和下一个字段。所以我们看到
just two words here. And there are some bit patterns in here, 0's and 1's. Okay
这里只有两个词。这里有一些位模式，0和1。好的
how do we know whether these are both pointers? It could be that one is a
我们怎么知道这两个都是指针呢？可能其中一个是
pointer and the, the other is not in the case of a list cell. So one of these
指针和，另一个不在列表单元格的情况下。所以其中一个
fields is just data like an injure and another one is a pointer. Or it could be
字段只是像伤害一样的数据，而另一个字段则是指针。或者也可能是
something like a binary tree node where both of these words are pointers. And
这两个词都是指针的二叉树节点。和
because of this weakness really in the C and C++ type systems, we just can't
因为在C和C++类型的系统中确实存在这个弱点，所以我们不能
guarantee that we know where all the pointers are. Now it turns out that it is
保证我们知道所有的指针在哪里。现在事实证明，它是
possible to extend garbage collection techniques to work with languages like C
可以将垃圾收集技术扩展到使用C++等语言
and C++. And the basic idea, or insight, is that it's always okay to be
和C++。最基本的想法，或者说洞察力是，总是可以
conservative. And if we're not sure whether something might be used in the
老气。如果我们不确定某些东西是否可以用在
future, then we will just keep it around. And remember that graph reachability is
未来，那我们就把它留在身边。记住，图的可达性是
already a conservative technique. What we really want is to keep around the objects
这已经是一种保守的技术了。我们真正想要的是把这些物体
that will just be used in the future, but the reachability in the object graph is an
这只会在将来使用，但对象图中的可达性是一个
approximation to that, so because reachable objects might be used. And now,
大致如此，因为可能会使用可到达的对象。而现在，
the problem with C and C++ is that we don't know where the pointers are. We
C和C++的问题是我们不知道指针在哪里。我们
don't have a guarantee from the type system about where the pointers are. And
类型系统不能保证指针在哪里。和
so the basic trick is that, if something looks like a pointer, then we will treat
所以基本的诀窍是，如果某个东西看起来像一个指针，那么我们将
it as a pointer. All we have to do is be conservative, and if we are not sure wh
它就像一个指针。我们所要做的就是保守一点，如果我们不确定
ether a given word of memory is a pointer. Then we can just treat it as a pointer,
以是，给定的内存字是一个指针。那么我们就可以把它当作一个指针，
and keep whatever it points to around. If we, and as long as we are not going to
把它指向的任何东西都留在身边。如果我们，只要我们不打算
move it or change it, that would be okay. And so, how, how do we decide whether a
移动它或改变它，那将是好的。那么，如何，我们如何决定一个
particular word of memory is a pointer? Well, it should be a line, meaning, you
内存中的特定字是指针吗？嗯，应该是一条线，意思是，你
know, it should end in some zeros to indicate that it was pointing, if it was a
知道吗，它应该以一些零结束，以指示它是指向的，如果它是
pointer it was pointing to a word boundary. And then, whatever pattern it
它指向单词边界的指针。然后，不管它是什么图案
is, if we interpret it as an address, it has to be a valid address. So, it should
就是，如果我们把它解释成一个地址，它就必须是一个有效的地址。所以，它应该是
point to the data segment. And Noah said, you know, these two conditions will rule
指向数据段。诺亚说，你知道，这两个条件将起决定作用
out all kinds of data and memory. So for example, any small integer is probably not
取出各种数据和内存。因此，例如，任何小整数都可能不是
going to be interpretable as a valid address in the data segment. So, you know,
将被解释为数据段中的有效地址。所以，你知道，
most likely, only things that are pointers, or very few things that are not
最有可能的是，只有是指针的东西，或者极少数不是指针的东西
pointers will be treated as pointers. And what we're going to do then, is, if it
指针将被视为指针。我们接下来要做的是，如果
looks like a pointer, we're going to consider it to be a pointer. We'll follow
看起来像一个指针，我们会认为它是一个指针。我们会跟着去的
it, and then we'll end up overestimating the set of reachable objects. We may keep
这样，我们就会高估可达对象集。我们可以继续
around some stuff, that isn't reachable at all. But that's alright, it's always okay
在一些东西周围，那是完全无法触及的。不过，没关系，一切都会好起来的
to keep around more stuff than necessary. Now, we still can't move the object,
留下更多不必要的东西。现在，我们仍然不能移动物体，
alright? Because we can't update the pointers to them. If we don't know that
好吗？因为我们无法更新指向它们的指针。如果我们不知道这一点
something is a pointer, we certainly don't want to change it, okay? And, you know,
有些东西是指针，我们当然不想改变它，好吗？而且，你知道，
for example, if we thought something was a pointer, and it was actually an account
例如，如果我们认为某物是一个指针，而它实际上是一个帐户
number, and then we updated the pointer, when we move the object, we would just
数字，然后我们更新指针，当我们移动对象时，我们只需
completely change what the program does. So, this only really works when you mark
完全改变程序的功能。所以，这只有在你标记的时候才能真正起作用
this way.
这边请。